<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--The following translations were generated by https://www.deepl.com/-->
  <!-- EN: Gramophone -->
  <Jecrell_Gramophone.label>Gramophone</Jecrell_Gramophone.label>
  <!-- EN: With a pawn selected, right click the gramophone to play a recorded song. When a song is playing, pawns may voluntarily listen to the music, or players can force them to listen by selecting listen to gramophone. -->
  <Jecrell_Gramophone.helpText>Lorsqu'un pion est sélectionné, faites un clic droit sur le gramophone pour jouer une chanson enregistrée. Lorsqu'une chanson est jouée, les pions peuvent volontairement écouter la musique, ou les joueurs peuvent les forcer à écouter en sélectionnant écouter le gramophone.</Jecrell_Gramophone.helpText>
  <!-- EN: Refrigerator -->
  <Jecrell_Refrigerator.label>Réfrigérateur</Jecrell_Refrigerator.label>
  <!-- EN: Refrigerators will hold a single stack of meals frozen. The meals will not display frozen in the game. Do not worry, for as long as they are inside a powered fridge, they will not spoil. -->
  <Jecrell_Refrigerator.helpText>Les réfrigérateurs peuvent contenir une seule pile de repas congelés. Les repas ne s'afficheront pas congelés dans le jeu. Ne vous inquiétez pas, tant qu'ils sont dans un réfrigérateur alimenté, ils ne se gâteront pas.</Jecrell_Refrigerator.helpText>
  <!-- EN: Writing -->
  <Jecrell_TypewriterTable.label>Écriture</Jecrell_TypewriterTable.label>
  <!-- EN: Pawns can use the typewriting table to give themselves joy and reduce stress. If Call of Cthulhu is enabled, this station will also reduce the severity of insanity at a faster rate. Pawns can also create journal items. Currently, these are rudimentary, and can be destroyed. They will be expanded upon later. -->
  <Jecrell_TypewriterTable.helpText>Les pions peuvent utiliser la table de dactylographie pour se donner du plaisir et réduire leur stress. Si l'Appel de Cthulhu est activé, cette station réduira également la gravité de la folie à un rythme plus rapide. Les pions peuvent également créer des articles de journal. Pour l'instant, ceux-ci sont rudimentaires et peuvent être détruits. Ils seront développés ultérieurement.</Jecrell_TypewriterTable.helpText>
  <!-- EN: Using Wax -->
  <Jecrell_Wax.label>Utilisation de la cire</Jecrell_Wax.label>
  <!-- EN: To make wax, select a cooking station or stove. Click the bills tab and select Make Wax. Meat from animals will be made into tallow wax. This wax can fuel non-electric candelabras or chandeliers. -->
  <Jecrell_Wax.helpText>Pour fabriquer de la cire, sélectionnez une station de cuisson ou un fourneau. Cliquez sur l'onglet Factures et sélectionnez Fabriquer de la cire. La viande des animaux sera transformée en cire de suif. Cette cire peut alimenter des candélabres ou des chandeliers non électriques.</Jecrell_Wax.helpText>
</LanguageData>
